AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs PHOTOS.247
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, [1958]-[2001].
  - Subseries B: Public Employee Press Contact Sheets, [1967]-[2001]
    - Vol. 29 Nos. 1-6 Issue Dates: Jan-Apr 1988 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 29 Nos. 7-13 Issue Dates: Apr-Aug 1988 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 29 Nos. 14-21 Issue Dates: Sep-Dec 1988 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 30 Nos. 1-5 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 30 Nos. 6-10 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1989, [Arp-Jun 1989] (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 30 Nos. 11-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 30 Nos. 15-17 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 30 Nos. 18-19 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 30 No. 20-Vol. 31 No. 1 Issue Dates: Nov 1989-Jan 1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 31 No. 2-7 Issue Dates: Feb-Apr 1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 31 No. 8-10 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1990 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 31 Nos. 11-15 Issue Dates: Jul-Oct 1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 31 Nos. 16-19 Issue Dates: Oct-Dec 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 31 No. 20-Vol. 32 No. 4 Issue Dates: Dec 1990-Feb 1991 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 32 Nos. 5-6 Issue Dates: Mar 1991 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 32 Nos. 7-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1991 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 32 Nos. 12-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Sep 1991 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 32 Nos. 15-17 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1991 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 32 Nos. 18-21 Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1991 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 1-5 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 6-7 Issue Dates: Apr 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 8-10 Issue Dates: May 1992 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 11-13 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 14-17 Issue Dates: Aug-Oct 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 33 Nos. 18-20 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1992 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 33 No. 21-Vol. 34 No. 3 Issue Dates: Dec 1992-Feb 1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 34 Nos. 4-7 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 34 Nos. 8-10 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1993 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 34 Nos. 11-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 34 Nos. 15-18 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 34 Nos. 19-20 Issue Dates: Nov 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 34 No. 21-Vol. 35 No. 3 Issue Dates: Dec 1993-Feb 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 35 Nos. 4-6 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1994 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 35 Nos. 7-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 35 Nos. 12-14 Issue Dates: Jul-Sep 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 35 Nos. 15-17 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 35 Nos. 18-19 Issue Dates: Nov 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 35 No. 20-Vol. 36 No. 3 Issue Dates: Dec 1994-Feb 1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 36 Nos. 4-6 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1995 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 36 Nos. 7-10 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1995 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 36 Nos. 11-13 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1995 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 36 Nos. 14-17 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1995 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 36 Nos. 18-21 Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 37 Nos. 1-4 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1996, [Jan-Feb 1996] (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 37 No. 5-7 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1996 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 37 Nos. 8-11 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1996 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 37 Nos. 12-13 Issue Dates: Jul-Aug 1996 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 37 Nos. 14-17 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1996 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 37 Nos. 18-20 Issue Dates: Nov 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 37 No. 21-Vol. 38 No. 4 Issue Dates: Dec 1996-Mar 1997 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 38 Nos. 5-7 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 38 Nos. 8-12 Issue Dates: Jun-Oct 1997 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 38 Nos. 13-16 Issue Dates: Oct-Dec 1997 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 39 Nos. 1-4 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1998 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 39 Nos. 5-7 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1998 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 39 Nos. 8-10 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 39 Nos. 12-14 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1998 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 39 Nos. 15-16 Issue Dates: Dec 1998 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 40 Nos. 3-4 Issue Dates: Mar 1999 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 40 Nos. 5-6 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1999 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 40 Nos. 7-8 Issue Dates: Jun 1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 40 Nos. 9-11 Issue Dates: Jul-Sep 1999 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 40 Nos. 12-15 Issue Dates: Oct-Dec 1999 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 41 Nos. 1-2 Issue Dates: Jan-Feb 2000 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 41 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 17, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 41 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 7, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 5 Issue Date: May 5, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 41 Nos. 5-7 Issue Dates: May-Jun 2000 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 41 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 7, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 41 Nos. 9-10 Issue Dates: Aug-Sep 2000 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 41 Nos. 11-12 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 2000 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 41 No. 13-Vol. 42 No. 1 Issue Dates: Dec 2000-Feb 2001 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 42 Nos. 2-3 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 2001 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue: Black History Month 2001, [Apr 2001] (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Oversize, 1977-2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Locals Contact Sheets, [1958]-1999.
    - Locals 154, 299, 371, 1963-1980, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Local 372, 1970-1990 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Local 372, 1991-1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Local 372, Undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Local 372, Undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Local 372, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Locals 374, 375, 376, 384, [1963]-1982, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Local 420, [1958]-1998, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Local 420, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes, [1967-1968] (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Locals 436, 461, 768, 924, 957, 983, 1965-1995, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Locals 1062, 1070, 1087, 1113, 1157, 1219, 1251, 1320, 1321, 1322, 1359, 1407, 1414, 1963-1993, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Locals 1455, 1457, 1482, 1485, 1503, 1505, 1506, 1507, 1982-1999, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Local 1549, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Local 1549: Triennial Shop Steward Education Conference, [Oct 1994] (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - [Local 1549], 1991-1994, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - [Local 1549], 1989-1995, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Local 1597, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Locals 1655, 1665, 1757, 1759, 1783, 1784, 1795, 1797, 1930, 1931, 1963-1990, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Local 1795 (Oversize), Undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Local 2021, 1971-1993, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Locals 2054, 2507, 2627, 2906, 1982-1988, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Blue Collar Division- Dotter Series (Locals 375, 1320, 1931), 1999, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Blue Collar Division- Locals Unknown, Undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Subseries D: DC 37 History Contact Sheets, [1958]-1995.
    - Events: March on Washington, [Aug 1963] (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Events: Civil Rights March--Montgomery, AL, [1965] (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, [Apr 1968] (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Events: Local 420 Strike, [1976] (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Events: Strikes and Demonstrations, Identified, [1958]-1982 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Events: Demonstrations and Rallies, Unidentified, 1977, undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Events: Identified, 1963-1995, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Events: Unidentified, [1980s], undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Events: Black History Month, 1988, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Officers and Staff: Victor Gotbaum, 1974-1978, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Officers and Staff: Lillian Roberts, 1977, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Officers and Staff: Former, Undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - [Members], 1967-1981, undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Members: Department of Parks, Undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Members: Police Civilians, Undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - AFSCME: Executive Board, Feb 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - AFSCME: DC 50, [1968-1969], undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Other Organizations: Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1977, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: DC 37 Subject Files Contact Sheets, 1963-1996.
    - Education, 1963-1982, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program, 1969, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Quality of Work Life (QWL), 1987-1991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Quality of Work Life (QWL), 1992-1994 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Quality of Work Life (QWL), 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Quality of Work Life (QWL), Undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Safety, 1972-1982, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Summer Camp, 1971-[1988], undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Various, 1982-[1995], undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Subseries F: General Subject Files Contact Sheets, 1973-1974.
    - General Subject Files, 1973-1974, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Negatives, [1948]-[2003].
  - Subseries A: Numbered Negatives, 1970-[2003].
    - DC 1 - DC 231, Oct 7, 1970-Oct 19, 1971 (Box 60)
    - DC 232 - DC 479, Oct 19, 1971-Jul 14, 1972 (Box 61)
    - DC 480 - DC 779, Jul 19, 1972-[May 10, 1973] (Box 62)
    - DC 780 - DC 1029, [May 9, 1973]-[Jan 1974] (Box 63)
    - DC 1030 - DC 1320, [Feb 5, 1974]-Dec 2, 1979 (Box 64)
    - DC 1321 - DC 1594, Dec 2, 1974-[Oct 28, 1975] (Box 65)
    - DC 1595 - DC 1828, [Oct 28, 1975]-Jun 22, 1976 (Box 66)
    - DC 1828 - DC 2050, Jun 23, 1976-Apr 21, 1977 (Box 67)
    - DC 2051 - DC 2279, Apr 21, 1977-Dec 12, 1977 (Box 68)
    - DC 2280 - DC 2505, Dec 12, 1977-Jul 15, 1978 (Box 69)
    - DC 2505 - DC 2699, Jul 15, 1978-Dec 8, 1978 (Box 70)
    - DC 2700 - DC 2952, Dec 11, 1978-[Jun 6, 1979] (Box 71)
    - DC 2953 - DC 3190, [Jun 7, 1979]-Nov 30, 1979 (Box 72)
    - DC 3191 - DC 3453, Dec 3, 1979-[Jun 16, 1980] (Box 73)
    - DC 3454 - DC 3749, [Jun 16, 1980]-[Feb 9, 1981] (Box 74)
    - DC 3750 - DC 4071, [Feb 9, 1981]-[Nov 17, 1981] (Box 75)
    - DC 4072 - DC 4340, [Nov 17, 1981]-[Jun 1982] (Box 76)
    - DC 4341 - DC 4575, Jun 16, 1982-Jan 24, 1983 (Box 77)
    - DC 4576 - DC 4966, Jan 21, 1983-Jan 23, 1984 (Box 78)
    - DC 4967 - DC 5175, Jan 26, 1984-Sep 3, 1984 (Box 79)
    - DC 5176 - DC 5399, [Sep 1984]-[May 1985] (Box 80)
    - DC 5400 - DC 5683, May 10, 1985-May 9, 1986 (Box 81)
    - DC 5685 - DC 7001, May 10, 1986-Sep 23, 1987 (Box 82)
    - DC 7002 - DC 8210, Sep 22, 1987-[Oct 1988] (Box 83)
    - DC 8211 - DC 8468, [Nov 1988]-Oct 7, 1989 (Box 84)
    - DC 8469 - DC 10763, [Oct 1989]-[Oct 1997] (Box 85)
    - GR 1 - GR 74, [Jun 17, 1982]-[Jun 15, 1983] (Box 85)
    - GR 76 - GR 193, [Jul 18, 1983]-[Jan 7, 1985] (Box 86)
    - GR 194 - GR 369, [Jan 7, 1985]-[Nov 21, 1986] (Box 87)
    - GR 370 - GR 543, [Nov 24, 1986]-[Nov 3, 1989] (Box 88)
    - GR 544 - GR 851, [Nov 3, 1989]-[Jun 9, 1993] (Box 89)
    - GR 852 - GR 1160, [Jun 11, 1993]-[Dec 26, 1995] (Box 90)
    - GR 1162 - GR 1345, [Dec 26, 1995]-[Jul 24, 1997] (Box 91)
    - GR 1346 - GR 1499, [Jul 25, 1997]-[May 13, 1999] (Box 92)
    - GR 1500 - GR 1640, [May 18, 1999]-[Oct 15, 2003] (Box 93)
    - CO 1 - CO 76, [Feb 11, 1999]-[Nov 2, 1999] (Box 93)
    - CO 77 - CO 219, [Nov 4, 1999]-[Sep 5, 2000] (Box 94)
    - CO 220 - CO 367, [Sep 6, 2000]-[May 30, 2001] (Box 95)
    - CO 368 - CO 533, [May 31, 2001]-[Jul 1, 2002] (Box 96)
    - CO 534 - CO 576, [Jul 1, 2002]-[Dec 9, 2002] (Box 97)
    - C - EF, [Oct 21, 1986]-[May 29, 1992] (Box 97)
    - [V] 45617 - V 45688 ("48 hrs. Negs"), [Oct 24-26, 1989] (Box 97)
    - V 845292, [Jun 13, 2000] (Box 97)
    - 3238-834513, May 8, 1981-[Apr 22, 2003] (Box 97)
  - Subseries B: Numbered 4x5 Negatives, [1971]-[1987].
    - DC 98 (2 negatives), [Apr 3, 1971] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - [DC] 11186-2, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - GR 394 (2 negatives), [Feb 23, 1987] (Box 59, Carton 3)
  - Subseries C: Public Employee Press Negatives, [1967]-[2001].
    - Vol. 8 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 29, 1967, [Mar 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 6 Issue Date: May 10, 1967, [May 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 21, 1967, [Jun 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 12, 1967, [Jul 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 23, 1967, [Aug 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 13, 1967, [Sep 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 4, 1967, [Oct 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 25, 1967, [Oct 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 15, 1967, [Nov 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. 14 Issue Date: Dec 6, 1967, [Dec 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 8 No. [16] Issue Date: Dec 27, 1967, [Dec 1967] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 9 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 24, 1968, [Jan 1968] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 9 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 28, 1968, [Feb 1968] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 9 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1968, [Mar 1968] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 9 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1968, [Apr 1968] (Box 57, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 9 No. 5 Issue Date: May 8, 1968, [May 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 6 Issue Date: May 29, 1968, [May 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 7 Issue Date: Jun 26, 1968, [Jun 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 24, 1968, [Jul 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 9 Issue Date: Sep 4, 1968, [Sep 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 25, 1968, [Sep 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 16, 1968, [Oct 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 6, 1968, [Nov 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 27, 1968, [Nov 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 9 No. 14 Issue Date: Dec 18, 1968, [Dec 1968] (Box 57, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 10 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 17, 1969, [Jan 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 7, 1969, [Feb 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 28, 1969, [Feb 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 21, 1969, [Mar 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 11, 1969, [Apr 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 6 Issue Date: May 2, 1969, [May 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 7 Issue Date: May 23, 1969, [May 1969] (Box 57, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 10 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 13, 1969, [Jun 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 11, 1969, [Jul 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 29, 1969, [Aug 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 19, 1969, [Sep 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 10, 1969, [Oct 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 31, 1969, [Oct 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 21, 1969, [Nov 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 10 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 12, 1969, [Nov 1969] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 11 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 2, 1970, [Jan 1970] (Box 57, Carton 4)
    - Vol. 11 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 30, 1970, [Jan 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 20, 1970, [Feb 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1970, [Mar 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1970, [Apr 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 6 Issue Date: May 8, 1970, [May 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 7 Issue Date: May 29, 1970, [May 1970] (Box 58, Carton 1)
    - Vol. 11 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 19, 1970, [Jun 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 11 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 10, 1970, [Jul 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 11 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 28, 1970, [Aug 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 11 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 18, 1970, [Sep 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 11 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 9, 1970, [Oct 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 11 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 30, 1970, [Oct 1970] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 12 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 1, 1971, [Jan 1971] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 12 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 29, 1971, [Jan 1971] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 13 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 11, 1972, [Feb 1972] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 13 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 2, 1972, [Jun 1972] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 15 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 7, 1974, [Jun 1974] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 16 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 8, 1975, [Aug 1975] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 19 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 21, 1978, [Apr 1978] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 19 No. 20 Issue Date: Dec 1, 1978, [Dec 1978] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 22 No. 8 Issue Date: May 15, 1981, [May 1981] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 23 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 16, 1982, [Jul 1982] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 25 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 27, 1984, [Jan 1984] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 28 No. 13 Issue Date: Aug 21, 1987, [Aug 1987] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 29 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 11, 1988, [Mar 1988] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 29 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 29, 1988, [Apr 1988] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 30 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 24, 1989, [Nov 1989] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 30 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 22, 1989, [Dec 1989] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 33 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 20, 1992, [Nov 1992] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 35 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 25, 1994, [Mar 1994] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 36 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 10, 1995, [Mar 1995] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 37 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 14, 1996, [Jun 1996] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 37 No. 12 Issue Date: Jul 5, 1996, [Jul 1996] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 37 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 29, 1996, [Nov 1996] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 39 No. 6 Issue Date: May 8, 1998, [May 1998] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 40 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 5, 1999, [Nov 1999] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 40 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 26, 1999, [Nov 1999] (Box 58, Carton 2)
    - Vol. 41 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 17, 2000, [Mar 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 7, 2000, [Apr 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 5 Issue Date: May 5, 2000, [May 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 7 Issue Date: Jun 16, 2000, [Jun 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 7, 2000, [Jul 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 9 Issue Date: Aug 31, 2000, [Aug 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000, [Sep 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 27, 2000, [Oct 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000, [Nov 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 13 Issue Date: Dec 15, 2000, [Dec 2000] (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 42 No. 1 Issue Date: Feb 2001 (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 42 No. 2 Issue Date: Mar 2001 (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue Date: Apr 2001 (Box 58, Carton 3)
    - "Census PEP 3/9", Undated (Box 58, Carton 3)
  - Subseries D: Public Employee Press 4x5 Negatives, [1969]-[2000].
    - Vol. 10 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 11, 1969, [Jul 1969] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 11 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1970, [Mar 1970] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 11 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1970 "SILENT SAM NEG.", [Mar 1970] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 11 No. 6 Issue Date: May 8, 1970, [May 1970] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 11 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 11, 1970 "Italy Feature" (17 negatives), [Dec 1970] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 15 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 21, 1974 "FLOWERS" (10 negatives), [Jun 1974] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 15 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 6, 1974 "Jean Walker Williams", [Dec 1974] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 16 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 14, 1975, [Mar 1975] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 17 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 12, 1976, [Mar 1976] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 18 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 15, 1977 (5 negatives), [Jul 1977] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 18 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 25, 1977, [Nov 1977] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 19 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 20, 1978, [Oct 1978] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 20 No. 20 Issue Date: Dec 7, 1979 (2 files), [Dec 1979] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 21 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 15, 1980, [Feb 1980] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 21 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 13, 1980, [Jun 1980] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 22 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 26, 1981, [Jun 1981] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 22 No. 14 Issue Date: Sep 11, 1981 (6 negatives), [Sep 1981] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 22 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 25, 1981 (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 23 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 22, 1982 (10 negatives), [Jan 1982] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 26 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 27, 1985, [Dec 1985] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 27 No. 19 Issue Date: Oct 31, 1986 (Includes "Dana Avant Blind Soc. Wkr.") (3 negatives), [Oct 1986] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 29 No. 13 Issue Date: Aug 19, 1988 (5 negatives), [Aug 1988] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 30 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 24, 1989 (5 negatives), [Feb 1989] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 31 No. 11 Issue Date: Jul 13, 1990, [Jul 1990] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 31 No. 12 Issue Date: Aug 24, 1990, [Aug 1990] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 31 No. 15 Issue Date: Oct 12, 1990 (4 negatives), [Oct 1990] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 32 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 11, 1991, [Jan 1991] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 32 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 22, 1991, [Feb 1991] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 32 No. 14 Issue Date: Sep 20, 1991 (2 negatives), [Sep 1991] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 32 No. 18 Issue Date: Nov 15, 1991, [Nov 1991] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 33 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 24, 1992 (2 negatives), [Jan 1992] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 33 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 4, 1992 "AIDS QUILT" (7 negatives), [Dec 1992] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 34 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 26, 1993 (Includes "CH testifies in WASH DC") (3 negatives), [Mar 1993] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 36 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 21, 1995, [Apr 1995] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 37 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 5, 1996 "Bob Taylor/Plaque", [Apr 1996] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 37 No. 8 Issue Date: May 3, 1996 "W. Haywood Burns, atty. Prof. of Law & Dean of the CUNY Law School 5/3/96", [May 1996] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 40 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 8, 1999 ("Copy negs handshake fotos citywide contract 1999") (2 negatives), [Oct 1999] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 40 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 17, 1999, [Dec 1999] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Vol. 41 No. 6 Issue Date: May 26, 2000 "Gorillas", [May 2000] (Box 59, Carton 3)
  - Subseries E: Locals Negatives, [1967]-[1999].
    - Local 154: "Menta Clock Repairers", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 299: Summer Playcamps [41556/2-3], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 371 (I), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 371 (II), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: "Zita's - Peter Stein/Hill 9/19/96" [10555], [Sep 1996] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: "Norman Davis's - retirees phonebank 11/96" [10511-2], [Nov 1996] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: "Summer '84 misc. Lewis - L372 at Grossingers 6/84" [5137/1-2], [1984] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: "Summer '84 misc. Ulysses Edwards-Audrey Campbell 5/8/84" [5138], [1984] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: "Sandra L372" [5139], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 372: [Shoot 1], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 375 (I), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 375 (II), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 375: "Dave Jacobson Dinner 5/68" [0,3,4], [May 1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 375: "Dave Jacobson Dinner 5/68" [5,6], [May 1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 376: "376 Meeting", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 (I), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 (II), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)